Guide to the George A. Romero Archival Collection, 1962-2017 SC.2019.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Publicity, 1962-2009; III.
  - Magazines, 1969-2010; 2.
    - Magazines, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 3)
      Variety 309, no. 3 (November 17, 1982) (2 copies), Prevue (May 1982), Alumni: Carnegie-Mellon University Alumni News 66, no. 1 (March 1982) (4 copies),Cinefantastique 12, no. 1 (February 1982), Cinefantastique 12, no. 2-3 (April 1982) (3 copies), Le Nouveau Film Francais International Edition no. 7 (May 20 1982).
    - Magazines, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      Film Criticism 7, no. 1 (Fall 1982) (3 copies), People Weekly (December 13, 1982) (2 copies), Esquire (January 1982) (4 copies), Film Comment (March-April 1982), Film Comment (September-October 1982), Newsweek (November 22, 1982), Screen International no. 11.
    - Magazines, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 2)
      Discover (July 1982), Time (November 22, 1982), Twilight Zone Magazine (September 1982), Twilight Zone Magazine (May 1982) (2 copies),Screen International Cannes 1982 Directory, Fangoria 20 (July 1982).
    - Magazines, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 3)
      Cinefantastique 13, no. 1 (4 copies).
    - Magazines, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 4)
      Actuel 42 (April 1983), Fantastic Films no. 32 (April 1983), Pleasure Hunt Magazine (January-February 1983), Pittsburgh Business Times (August 22-28, 1983), Pittsburgh Magazine (September 1983).
    - Magazines, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      Cinefantastique 15, no. 3 (July 1985), Film Comment (June 1985), Us Magazine (February 11, 1985).
    - Magazines, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 6)
      The Film Journal 90, no. 5 (May 1987).
    - Magazines, 1988 (Box 88, Folder 1)
      Rolling Stone no. 530/531 (July 14 1988), Time (August 8, 1988) (2 copies), Cinefantastique 10, no. 5 (July 1988), Stick no. 2, Newsweek (August 8, 1988) (3 copies), Daily Variety (April 25, 1998).
    - Magazines, 1989 (Box 88, Folder 2)
      Cinefantastique 19, no. 3, People Weekly (January 9, 1989), The Disney Channel Magazine (December 20 1987-January 30, 1998), Oakland 2, no. 12.
    - Magazines, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 3)
      Cinefantastique 21, no. 3.
    - Magazines, 1991 (Box 88, Folder 4)
      Pittsburgh Magazine (January 1991) (6 copies).
    - Press kits for Pittsburgh Magazine (5 copies), January 1991 (Box 88, Folder 5)
      Press kit for George A. Romero cover story. Includes photo, press release, copy of magazine.
    - Magazines, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 6)
      Daily Variety (March 20, 1992) (2 copies), Publishers Weekly (June 22, 1992), Daily Variety Oct 14 1992, Omni 14, no. 9 (June 1992), Omni 14, no. 12 (September 1992), Omni 15, no. 1 (October 1992), Circuito Cinema no. 44 (July 1992).
    - Magazines, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 1)
      Daily Variety (April 21, 1993), The Hollywood Reporter (April 22, 1993), Entertainment Weekly (April 16, 1993), Rolling Stone no. 655 (April 29, 1993), Rolling Stone no. 656 (May 11 1993), Fangoria no. 121 (April 1993), Fangoria no. 122 (May 1993), Cinefantastique 24, no. 1 (June 1993), The Hollywood Reporter (March 11, 1993), Premiere 6, no. 9 (May 1993) (2 copies).
    - Magazines, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 2)
      Simulacres (Autumn 1999), Pittsburgh Magazine (Deecember 1999) (2 copies), Time (December 20, 1999), Video Watchdog no. 54.
    - Magazines, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 3)
      Simulacres (Winter 2000), Arcade no. 17 (March 2000), The Hollywood Reporter (October 31-November 6, 2000), CineAction no. 53 (2 copies).
    - Magazines, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 4)
      DGA Magazine (January 2000) (7 copies).
    - Magazines, 2002 (Box 90, Folder 1)
      Film Haftet no. 119, filmcritica no. 523 (March 2002).
    - Magazines, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 2)
      Daily Variety (July 15 2004) (2 copies), La Cosa Cine Fantastico no. 100 (June 2004).
    - Magazines, 2005 (Box 90, Folder 3)
      Entertainment Weekly (June 17, 2005) (4 copies), Fangoria (June 2005) (8 copies).
    - Magazines, 2005 (Box 90, Folder 4)
      The Hollywood Reporter (June 20, 2005) (3 copies), The Hollywood Reporter (June 21-27, 2005) (2 copies), Daily Variety (June 20, 2005) (6 copies).
    - Magazines, May 2008 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      Cannabis Culture no. 70.
    - Magazines, 2009 (Box 90, Folder 6)
      Game Informer no. 199.
    - Magazines, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 7)
      Famous Monsters of Filmland no. 252 (December 2010), Pacific Beach Collective 2, no. 1 (January 2010), Culture (March 2010).
  - Festival Programs and Cinema Calendars, 1970-2009; 3.
    This subseries contains programs, calendars, and other materials for film festivals, film screenings, and events.
    - Museum of Modern Art Department of Film "An Evening with George Romero" program notes, June 16, 1970 (Box 91, Folder 1)
      3 copies.
    - Walter Reade Selected Film Guide, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Don Pancho's calendar, 1976 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - 6e Festival International de Paris du Film Fantastique et de Science-Fiction program, March 1977 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - 30th Cannes Film Festival official guide, May 1977 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - International Hofer Filmtage, October 27-30, 1977 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - 4-Star Cinema film calendar, September 1978 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Los Angeles International Film Exposition offical catalogue, March 1979 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - 23rd London Film Festival program notes (2 copies) and film guide, November 1979 (Box 91, Folder 9)
      2 copies of single page on "Zombies" [Dawn of the Dead].
    - American Film Institute "Films That Got Away" program notes, 1979 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - University Art Museum Berkeley calendar, February 1980 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Carnegie Institute Musem of Art Film Calendar, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Suntory Tokyo International Fantastic Film Festival, October 1988 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Valencia Community College's "The Art of Horror" brochure, October 22, 1993 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - The Film Society of Lincoln Center's Walter Reade Theater programs, November 1993 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Zombie Jamboree! Night of the Living Dead 25th Anniversary and Horror Exposition souvenir program book, August 1993 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - The 1st Annual Directors Retreat (Directors Guild of America), September 1997 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - 18th Torino Film Festival program, November 2000 (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - 19th Torino Film Festival program, November 2001 (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - Cinematheque Francaise program, November/December 2004 (Box 91, Folder 20)
      8 copies.
    - 13th Annual Dusty Film Festival and Awards program, June 2002 (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - Moving Image Quarterly, January-March 2003 (Box 91, Folder 22)
      5 copies.
    - 58th Cannes Film Festival official program, May 2005 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Cinevegas Film Festival program, June 2005 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - 24th Sundance Film Festival program, January 2008 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Museum of the Moving Image Diary of the Dead preview screenings program note, February 6, 2008 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - 66th Venice Film Festival program, 2009 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Promotional Materials, circa 1967-2009; IV.
  This series contains materials created to publicize films and other work by George A. Romero. It includes posters and other materials for wide release, press releases, and promotional materials created for individual screenings. Festival programs and cinema calendars are categorized in their own series.
  - The Latent Image color logo, undated (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Latent Image Blue Cross promotional flier, 1970 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    2 copies of "Blue Cross Bulletin" flier with focus on Latent Image as customer.
  - Latent Image/Night of the Living Dead notebook, 1968-1978 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    Primarily photocopies of promotional materials and press clippings relating to the original release of Night of the Living Dead from 1968-1972. Includes cast and crew photographies, photocopies of promotional photos, as well as limited similar materials for "Sword of Survinski," a sponsored film about maple syrup, and Martin.
  - Night of the Living Dead German small poster, undated (Box 93, Folder 4)
    With tagline "Schwache Nerven soliten wissen, in diesem Schocker werden Opfer nicht nur zerbissen!!!"
  - Drawings for Latent Image Christmas card, undated (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Latent Image/Laurel Tape & Film press release, undated (Box 93, Folder 6)
    Undated, likely 1974-1975. "Introducing George Romero/Richard Rubinstein." Includes mention of The Amusement Park, The Winners, and a list of industrial films, p.r films/sales & promo, and political films.
  - There's Always Vanilla premiere invitation, 1972 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - The Crazies press releases (1976 re-release) (Box 93, Folder 8)
    7 copies of longer press release (reviews & synopsis), 6 copies shorter press release (review, synopsis, credits list), loose sheets of announcement, synopsis, credits.
  - Martin promotional materials, 1977-1978 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    Includes invitation to special screening, invitation to additional screening, invitation to Utah/U.S. Film Festival Awards Evening, press releases, list of press quotes, glossy ad for novelization, ad mock-ups, 2 copies of flier for midnight screenings at Waverly Theatre, and playdate schedules.
  - Dawn of the Dead promotional materials, 1978-1979 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    2 press releases in black and white Dawn of the Dead folder: 1 longer (12 photographs including pen-autographed photo of George Romero, synopsis, photocopy of Rolling Stone review); 1 copy shorter (5 photographs including Dario Argento and George Romero on set, synopsis, release for novelization, release for Argento/Romero collaboration - also includes color postcard of JFK assassination locations); loose copied sheets of Romero biography, synopsis, black and white photocopied poster, press releases.
  - Dawn of the Dead official poster book, undated (Box 93, Folder 11)
    9 copies, one autographed by Tom Savini.
  - Dawn of the Dead promotional materials, 1978-1995 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    Flier for Document of the Dead screening, Portuguese-language poster, 3 copies German-language poster, 2 copies English-language European press kit in full-color folder w/press releases, synopsis, credits and biographies, novelization book jacket, cardboard Japanese-language promo, 2 German-language press kits (1 shorter, b&w; 2 copies full color, bound, longer), Italian poster, 8.5x11 folded color poster/flier, Japanese full-color bound press kit, large-format German-language poster, German VHS cover.
  - Dawn of the Dead premiere invitations, 1978-1979 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    2 copies of ticket for premiere at Gateway Theatre in Downtown Pittsburgh. Invitation to cocktail party.
  - Knightriders promotional materials, 1980-1981 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    1 color promotional flier, 2 black and white copies.
  - Creepshow promotional materials, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    Press kit in color folder (1 sheet of headshot photos, credits, production information, biographies of George Romero and Stephen King, synopsis), photocopy of French-language promotional kit, loose synopsis, announcement of principal photography.
  - Creepshow folder for Laurel Entertainment, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    Includes summary of publicity activities, press clippings, ad photocopies.
  - Fangoria posters, undated (Box 93, Folder 18)
    3 Creepshow and 1 Day of the Dead poster centerfolds from Fangoria magazine.
  - Day of the Dead promotional material, undated (Box 94, Folder 1)
    Press activities list and small, folded poster.
  - Pittsburgh Filmmakers George A. Romero Festival posters, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    4 copies. Includes full listing of films and events on back.
  - Monkey Shines promotional material, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    Premiere invitation, press kit in b&w folder (credits, production information, biographies of George Romero, Charles Evans, Peter Grunwald, Gerald S. Paonessa, "fact sheet").
  - Monkey Shines Spanish Language mini-poster [Monerias Diabolicas], 1988-89 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Two Evil Eyes promotional material, 1990 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    VHS cover, color bound press kit (photos, credits, synopsis, biographies of Dario Argento and George Romero).
  - Night of the Living Dead (1990) DVD cover mock-up, 1999 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Night of the Living Dead (1990) press kit (Box 94, Folder 7)
    Includes promotional photographs, production information, cast & crew. In color folder.
  - The Dark Half promotional materials, 1993 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    Includes magnet, 15 VIP invites, 1 invite to private screening, color flier.
  - Bruiser promotional materials, undated (Box 94, Folder 9)
    Japanese flyer, George Romero biography, mini-poster.
  - Land of the Dead promotional materials, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    Invite to cast screening, envelope with invites and information for Steeltown benefit screening, sheet with two photographs.
  - Land of the Dead Stephen King preview: "Long Time Dead, Still Alive", 2005 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Land of the Dead press day schedule, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Land of the Dead Cannes packet, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Land of the Dead premiere materials, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Survival of the Dead Japanese press booklets, 2009 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    Full color Japanese booklet (press kit?) for Survival; 6 copies.
  - "Stay Scared!" stickers for georgearomero.com, circa 2000-2010 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    Box containing one roll of stickers.
  - Night of the Living Dead Continental Films ad, 1968 (Map-case 34-1, Folder 1)
  - Night of the Living Dead original film poster, 1968 (Map-case 34-1, Folder 2)
  - Night of the Living Dead [La Notte Dei Morti Viventi] banner style poster, Italian, undated (Map-case 34-1, Folder 3)
  - Night of the Living Dead 25th anniversary poster, 1993 (Map-case 34-1, Folder 4)
  - There's Always Vanilla original film poster, 1971 (Map-case 34-1, Folder 5)
  - Martin London Film Festival poster, 1977 (Map-case 34-1, Folder 6)
  - Martin original film poster, 1977 (Map-case 34-1, Folder 7)
  - Martin original film poster, skeleton hand design, 1977 (Map-case 34-1, Folder 8)
  - Dawn of the Dead original film poster, 1978 (Map-case 34-2, Folder 1)
  - Dawn of the Dead EMI Video release poster, 1978 (Map-case 34-2, Folder 2)
  - Dawn of the Dead film poster, comic book art style design, circa 1978 (Map-case 34-2, Folder 3)
  - Dawn of the Dead [Zombies] film poster, United Kingdom version, 1978 (Map-case 34-2, Folder 4)
  - Dawn of the Dead [Zombie] film poster, German version, 1978 (Map-case 34-2, Folder 5)
  - Dawn of the Dead [Zombie] banner style poster, German, 1978 (Map-case 34-2, Folder 6)
  - Creepshow original film poster, 1982 (Map-case 34-2, Folder 7)
  - Creepshow original film poster, comic book version, 1982 (Map-case 34-2, Folder 8)
  - Monkey Shines original film poster, 1988 (Map-case 34-3, Folder 1)
  - Monkey Shines original film poster, copy 2, 1988 (Map-case 34-3, Folder 2)
  - Monkey Shines collage poster of cast and crew, 1988 (Map-case 34-3, Folder 3)
  - Night of the Living Dead original film poster, German, 1990 (Map-case 34-3, Folder 4)
  - The Dark Half original film poster, 1993 (Map-case 34-3, Folder 5)
  - Bruiser original film poster, 2000 (Map-case 34-3, Folder 6)
  - Land of the Dead original film poster, skyline version, 2005 (Map-case 34-3, Folder 7)
  - Land of the Dead original film poster, hand on fence version, 2005 (Map-case 34-3, Folder 8)
  - Survival of the Dead original film poster, 2009 (Map-case 34-3, Folder 9)
  - Survival of the Dead original film poster, Japanese version, 2009 (Map-case 34-3, Folder 10)
  - Speeches, unpublished interviews, biographies, and short non-fiction writings by George A. Romero, circa 1980-2012
    Includes speech on the MPAA ratings system (circa 1979) and biographical speech (circa 2000-2005).
    - George A. Romero speech on MPAA ratings system, includes handwritten notes and Jack Valenti essay "The Movie Rating System: How It Began", undated (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - George A. Romero biographical speech (fragment), undated (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - George A. Romero short piece on I Walked with a Zombie, March 15, 1998 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - George A. Romero brief biographies (not tied to specific project), undated (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - "Zombie Town Hall" intro and transcript, with George A. Romero, Steven Schlozman, and Max Brooks, 2012 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - "Creepshow reminiscence", undated (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Short non-fiction writings by George A. Romero, undated (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Interview transcript with George A. Romero, November 29, 1985
- Legal Documents, 1970-2012; V.
  This series contains contracts and legal correspondence not related to a specific project. Legal documents related to a named project can be found in "Production Materials."
  - New Line contracts and correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Laurel Entertainment letter to shareholders, February 15, 1983 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Laurel Entertainment folder, January 1983 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    Includes fiscal reports, Creepshow poster, Stephen King poster, list of upcoming projects.
  - Laurel Entertainment folder, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    Includes annual report, press clippings, first quarter report.
  - RGP Legal documents, 1990-1999 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    Contracts and correspondence regarding various unnamed projects involving George A. Romero and Peter Grunwald, including with New Line, Tartan Films, and Carnegie-Mellon University.
  - Tax Identification Paperwork, 2011 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - New Line first look agreement, December 4, 1991 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Laurel legal documents, 1976-1988 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Latent Image legal documents, 1970-1988 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Personal legal documents and correspondence, 1979-1988 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Miramax proposal, October 1993 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Personal legal and business documents, 1990-2012 (Box 97, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1977-2004; VI.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This series contains correspondence not tied to any specific productions.
  - Fan Letters, 1998-1999 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Proposed projects, 1988-2004 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Teaching, 1995-1999 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Work inquiries, 1996-2003 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Personal, 1995-2001 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Festivals, Events, & Honors, 1977-2000 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Other filmmakers, 1996-1999 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    Includes letter to John Carpenter, invitation to 1997 fundraising screening of The Blair Witch Project, letter from Emilio Estevez, letter about Jonathan Demme/Silence of the Lambs, detailed response to draft of a novel by Steven Schlozman.
  - Interview inquiries, 1995-2000 (Box 98, Folder 8)
- Photographs, circa 1950s-2017; VII.
  This series contains photographs including publicity and behind the scenes photos from film set; candid shots; event photos; and personal and family photographs. All photos are positive prints or slides unless otherwise noted as negatives.
  - Night of the Living Dead (1968) photo album, circa 1967-69; 52 Photographic Prints (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Night of the Living Dead (1968) production and behind the scenes stills, circa 1967-69; 22 Photographic Prints (Box 99, Folder 2-3)
  - Season of the Witch production and behind the scenes stills, circa 1970-72; 36 Photographic Prints (Box 99, Folder 4-5)
  - The Crazies production and behind the scenes stills, circa 1972-74; 22 Photographic Prints (Box 99, Folder 6-7)
  - The Amusement Park production and behind the scenes stills, circa 1973; 237 Photographic Prints (Box 99, Folder 8-11)
  - The Winners behind the scenes photos, circa 1973; 2 Photographic Prints (Box 99, Folder 12)
    Photo of Terry Bradshaw in the Steelers lockerroom and O.J. Simpson playing tennis.
  - Martin behind the scenes photos, circa 1975-1977; 14 Photographic Prints (Box 99, Folder 13)
    Behind the scenes photos from production of Martin. Also includes photo of marquee featuring film title from unknown cinema.
  - Martin behind the scenes photo scrapbook, circa 1975-76; 98 Photographic Prints (Oversize 102, Item 1)
    Scrapbook with behind the scenes photos from production of Martin and includes annotations from Christine Forrest Romero. Also includes two press clippings with advertisements for the film.
  - Dawn of the Dead production and behind the scenes stills, circa 1977-78; 18 Photographic Prints (Box 99, Folder 14-15)
  - Dawn of the Dead slides and photo of billboard from Rivoli Theatre in NYC, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Knightriders production and behind the scenes stills, 1981; 41 Photographic Prints (Box 100, Folder 1-3)
  - Knightriders behind the scenes photos, 1980; 23 Photographic Prints (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Knightriders production and behind the scenes slides, May - August 1980; 661 Photographic Slides (Box 100, Folder 5-7)
  - Knightriders production and behind the scenes slides, July 1980; 10 Sheets; 190 Photographic Slides (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Knightriders production and behind the scenes slides, August 1980; 9 Sheets; 169 Photographic Slides (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Creepshow production and behind the scenes stills, circa 1981-83; 39 Photographic Prints (Box 100, Folder 8-11)
  - Creepshow animation still, undated; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Day of the Dead production and behind the scenes stills, circa 1983-86; 14 Photographic Prints (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Monkey Shines production and behind the scenes stills, circa 1987-89; 6 Photographic Prints (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Monkey Shines contact sheets, circa 1987-89; 42 Sheets (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - The Dark Half production and behind the scenes stills, circa 1990-93; 4 Photographic Prints (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - The Dark Half cast photo, 1990-1991; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Jacaranda Joe photos of creature, 1994; 2 Photographic Prints (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Photo of Romero with actress Nina Garbiras on set of Bruiser, circa 1999-2000; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Photo of Romero with Dennis Hopper from Land of the Dead set, circa 2003-2005; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Land of the Dead digital thumbnail prints D001, October 22, 2004; 15 Sheets (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Land of the Dead digital thumbnail prints D002, October 28, 2004; 15 Sheets (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Land of the Dead digital thumbnail prints D3, October 28, 2004; 13 Sheets (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Land of the Dead digital thumbnail prints D04, November 5, 2004; 19 Sheets (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Land of the Dead digital thumbnail prints D05, November 10, 2004; 9 Sheets (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Land of the Dead digital thumbnail prints D06, November 10, 2004; 15 Sheets (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Land of the Dead digital thumbnail prints D007, D008, D009, November 15, 2004; 11 Sheets (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Land of the Dead digital thumbnail prints D010, November 15, 2004; 13 Sheets (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - Land of the Dead digital thumbnail prints D011, November 23, 2004; 28 Sheets (Box 101, Folder 15)
    Contains behind the scenes photos of Greg Nicotero applying makeup effects.
  - Land of the Dead digital thumbnail prints D012, December 01, 2004; 13 Sheets (Box 101, Folder 16)
    Contains behind the scenes and on set photos of Simon Pegg and Edgar Wright.
  - Land of the Dead digital thumbnail prints D014, D015, D016, December 07, 2004; 15 Sheets (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - Land of the Dead digital thumbnail prints D017, December 17, 2004; 24 Sheets (Box 101, Folder 18)
  - Land of the Dead digital thumbnail prints D018, December 21, 2004; 18 Sheets (Box 101, Folder 19)
  - Diary of the Dead release party photos, circa 2007; 5 Photographic Prints (Box 101, Folder 20)